const easyQuestions = [
    {
        question: "How many points does a player get for playing 60 minutes or more?",
        answers: [1,2,3],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How many points does a goalkeeper get for every 3 shots saved?",
        answers: [1,2,3],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many points does a defender get for scoring a goal?",
        answers: [4,5,6],
        correctAnswer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "How many points does a player get for assisting a goal?",
        answers: [3,4,5],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How many points does a defender get for a clean sheet?",
        answers: [3,4,5],
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How many points does a goalkeeper get for a clean sheet?",
        answers: [3,4,5],
        correctAnswer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How many points does a forward get for scoring a goal?",
        answers: [4,5,6],
        correctAnswer: 4
    }, 
    {
        question: "How many points does a player get for a yellow card?",
        answers: [-1,-2,-3],
        correctAnswer: -1
    },
];

const hardQuestions = [
    {
        question: "How many points does a goalkeeper get for a penalty save?",
        answers: [3,4,5],
        correctAnswer: 5
    },  
    {
        question: "How many points does a player get for a red card?",
        answers: [-1,-2,-3],
        correctAnswer: -3
    },
    {
        question: "How many points does a player get for each own goal?",
        answers: [-1,-2,-3],
        correctAnswer: -2
    },
    {
        question: "How many points does a player get for missing a penalty?",
        answers: [-1,-2,-3],
        correctAnswer: -2
    },
    {
        question: "How many points does a goalkeeper get for every 2 goals conceded?",
        answers: [-1,-2,-3],
        correctAnswer: -1
    },
    {
        question: "How many points does a defender get for every 2 goals conceded?",
        answers: [-1,-2,-3],
        correctAnswer: -1
    },
    {
        question: "How many points does a goalkeeper get for scoring a goal?",
        answers: [4,5,6],
        correctAnswer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "How many points does a midfielder get for scoring a goal?",
        answers: [3,4,5],
        correctAnswer: 5
    },
];
